First Love is a romance, drama film directed by A.J. Edwards.
A young man’s difficult entry into adulthood, who experiences the highs and lows of his first love,
while dealing with the familial fallout spurred by the financial crisis of 2008.
Jim Albright, played by Hero Fiennes Tiffin.
Ann Matienzo, played by Sydney Park.
Kay Albright, played by Diane Kruger.
Greg Albright, played by Jeffrey Donovan.
Father Alex, played by Nikolai Tsankov.
Casey Albright, played by Chris Galust.
First Love is a 2022 American romance film written and directed by A.
Edwards and starring Diane Kruger, Hero Fiennes
Tiffin, Sydney Park and Jeffrey Donovan.
The story follows how Jim and Ann meet, lose
contact and their lives eventually join.
The film was released on June 17, 2022 in the United States.
The tone is emotional.